Celestial Avenue is a drama, romance, comedy film directed by Cameron Cairnes.
Kath is looking for love in all the wrong places.
In Chinatown in the middle of a less than successful blind date, she
overhears the soulful Cantonese singing of Ah Gong.
Kath is intrigued.
Is there more to Ah Gong than meets the eye?
Joel, played by Jason Gann.
Kath, played by Catherine Moore.
Ah Gong, played by Angus Sampson.
Madame Wong, played by Gabrielle Chan.
Chef Wong, played by Jin Yi.
RBD was a Mexican Latin pop group that gained popularity from
Televisa's telenovela Rebelde (2004–2006).
It was composed of Anahí, Dulce María, Maite Perroni, Alfonso
Herrera, Christopher von Uckermann and Christian Chávez.
The group achieved international success from 2004 until their separation in 2009 and sold over 15 million
records worldwide, making them one of the best-selling Latin music artists of all time.
In November 2004, the group released their debut
studio album, Rebelde, to great success.
In September 2005, the group released their second album, Nuestro Amor, receiving
their first Latin Grammy Award nomination at the 2006 ceremony.
In 2006, the group released their third album, Celestial; this was their
first album to be released simultaneously in all countries.
The album's lead single, "Ser o Parecer", topped the Billboard
Hot Latin Songs chart for two consecutive weeks.
In the same year, the group released their fourth album, and
first English-language project titled Rebels.
In 2007, the group released their fifth album  Empezar Desde Cero,
which was nominated at the Latin Grammy Awards.
In 2009, the group released their sixth and final album, Para Olvidarte De Mí.
RBD officially formed on 30 October 2004, and announced on 15 August 2008,
through a press release, that they would disband on 10 March 2009.
In September 2020, the band announced they would reunite through a virtual show in
December, and their music was released on digital platforms the same month.
Four of the original members returned: Maite Perroni, Anahí,
Christopher von Uckermann and Christian Chávez.
Almost three years later, on 19 January 2023, they announced that all members would return for a
one-off tour, titled Soy Rebelde Tour, with the exception of Alfonso Herrera.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.